<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Dicoding Football</string>
    <string name="favorites">Favorites</string>
    <string name="teams">Teams</string>
    <string name="next_match">Next Match</string>
    <string name="last_match">Last Match</string>
    <string name="vs">VS</string>
    <string name="added_fav">Added to Favorite</string>
    <string name="removed_fav">Removed to Favorite</string>
    <array name="league">
        <item>English Premier League</item>
        <item>English League Championship</item>
        <item>German Bundesliga</item>
        <item>Italian Serie A</item>
        <item>French Ligue 1</item>
        <item>Spanish La Liga</item>
    </array>
    <string-array name="club_name">
        <item>Barcelona</item>
        <item>Real Madrid</item>
        <item>Bayern Munchen</item>
        <item>Manchester City</item>
        <item>Manchester United</item>
        <item>Chelsea</item>
        <item>AC Milan</item>
        <item>Arsenal</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="spinner">
        <item>German Bundesliga</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="club_desc">
        <item>Known simply as Barcelona and colloquially as Barça, is a professional football club based in Barcelona, Catalonia, Spain.</item>
        <item>Commonly known as Real Madrid, is a professional football club based in Madrid, Spain.</item>
        <item>Commonly known as FC Bayern München, FCB, Bayern Munich, or FC Bayern, is a German sports club based in Munich, Bavaria (Bayern). It is best known for its professional football team, which plays in the Bundesliga, the top tier of the German football league system, and is the most successful club in German football history, having won a record 28 national titles and 18 national cups.</item>
        <item>Manchester City Football Club, commonly known as City, is a football club in Manchester, England. Founded in 1880 as St. Mark\'s (West Gorton), it became Ardwick Association Football Club in 1887 and Manchester City in 1894. The club\'s home ground is the City of Manchester Stadium in east Manchester, to which it moved in 2003, having played at Maine Road since 1923.</item>
        <item>Manchester United Football Club, commonly known as Man. United or simply United, is a professional football club based in Old Trafford, Greater Manchester, England, that competes in the Premier League, the top flight of English football. Nicknamed "the Red Devils", the club was founded as Newton Heath LYR Football Club in 1878, changed its name to Manchester United in 1902 and moved to its current stadium, Old Trafford, in 1910.</item>
        <item>Chelsea Football Club is a professional football club in London, England, that competes in the Premier League. Founded in 1905, the club\'s home ground since then has been Stamford Bridge.</item>
        <item>Associazione Calcio Milan, commonly referred to as A.C. Milan or simply Milan, is a professional football club in Milan, Italy, founded in 1899.</item>
        <item>Arsenal Football Club is a professional football club based in Islington, London, England, that plays in the Premier League, the top flight of English football. The club has won 13 League titles, a record 13 FA Cups, two League Cups, the League Centenary Trophy, 15 FA Community Shields, one UEFA Cup Winners\' Cup and one Inter-Cities Fairs Cup.</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="club_image">
        <item>@drawable/barca</item>
        <item>@drawable/madrid</item>
        <item>@drawable/bayern</item>
        <item>@drawable/city</item>
        <item>@drawable/mu</item>
        <item>@drawable/chelsea</item>
        <item>@drawable/milan</item>
        <item>@drawable/arsenal</item>
    </array>
</resources>
